(Amy:)between two pieces of acrylic.
(Penny:)Oh, it's a snowflake
from the North Pole.
(Penny:)Leonard gave it
to me last year.
(Bernadette:)Oh, God, that is so romantic.
(Penny:)Yeah, it was.
(Bernadette:)Leonard's really one of a kind.
(Amy:)Saying that
while holding a snowflake
is a bit heavy-handed,
don't you think?
(Penny:)Let me see that.
(Penny:)Oh, screw it.
(Penny:)I can deal with
a little self-loathing.
(Penny:)Let's go find me
a heinie to bite.
(Amy:)Outstanding.
(Amy:)And if we fail,
we can always stop at CVS
(Amy:)and pick you out
a nice toothbrush.
I call mine "Gerard."
(Bernadette:)That's kind of creepy.
♪ Don't go breaking
my heart ♪
♪ I couldn't
if I tried ♪
♪ Oh, honey,
if I get restless ♪
♪ Baby, you're
not that kind ♪